
Executive Rooms


Description: All these rroms have enough space, a desk for a work, a cable TV and a wireless connection.There's room                     service

Chambres doubles:


Description: Toutes ces chambres ont assez d'espace avec une table de travail, TV avec des chaines satellites ainsi qu'un  
             reseau internet sans fil.
QUANTITY: 
-Double bed/ lit double (1.50m/2m)
-Bathroom/douche
-Cable TV/TV satellite
-Office/bureau
-WIFI Wireless Connection/reseau internet sans fil

Price/Prix: 60$ for a sigle person
            70$ for a married couple
            80$ for a couple with one child.

Eng: Full breakfast is included in the room rate
Fr : Le petit dejeuner est inclus au tariff de la chambre