Suite(Executive Appartment)


Description: This room has enough space to sit with friends and family, a kitchen and a mini bar.
             Do you want to cook your prefered food? Count on the hotel staff and they will help you
             shopping whether you want extra ingredients, whether you need a hand of the chef in your 
             appartment kitchen.
             

Suite (Appartement)


Description: Cette chambre possede assez d'espace pour des amis ou famille, une cuisine ainsi qu'un mini bar.
             Souhaitez-vous faire de la cuisine de votre plat favori? Comptez sur le staff de l'hotel et ils vous
             aideront dans l'achat si vous voulez d'autres ingredients locaux, ou si vous voulez une aide du chef
             de cuisine de l'hotel.

QUANTITY/quantite 
-Double bed/ lit double 
-Bathroom/douche
-Telephone
-Cable TV/TV satellite(DSTV)
-Office/bureau
-WIFI Wireless Connection/reseau internet sans fil

Price/Prix: 120$

Eng: Full breakfast is included in the room rate 
Fr : Le petit dejeuner est inclus au tariff de la chambre 